Like waiting when you run GC.
If you're a woman, you have to add extra dishes.
The flags no, not really.
Yeah, code.
I have folders like, uhm,
it, yeah yeah, like it doesn't actually make any difference.
It sucks to write code and debug things,
even if you're a lady.
But here's something kind of neat.
If you're a woman, or if you're like underrepresented in
your hobby or profession,
you're going to be underestimated a lot,
which is very powerful, right?
'cause they've never see you coming,
so I've tried to use that as like my special
power 'cause.
People like, oh, there's no way like she's gonna do
this like there's no way she'll she'll design this it's
just no way they'll put me out of business and
I put
them out of business and then you.
And then you're the
first woman on the
cover of Wired magazine. Just take him out.
Yeah yeah that's awesome.
I love that perspective yeah,
so that that's that's my I'm I'm using this as
as as as a technique.
It's like you you look so harmless that
it's a testament to to open source too as well.
And how are you able to?
One put together kits for things you were interested in
at the time,
and maybe other folks are interested in.
Yeah, but also being able to grow community around this
too as well.
So have you seen? Like Adafruit wasn't the first project
company to put together kits for hardware computers,
but are you seeing a trend and folks really adopting
hardware computing through?
I guess interacting with
Adafruit. Well I I think so.
My my thing is, I personally find engineering and making
electronics and all this stuff very interesting.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I buy personally like it,
I enjoy it. I think that trying to convince.
People that electronics and computing is interesting on its own
terms is not a good idea.
Like I, I really don't like how every book that's
about like like I'm going to learn electronics.
I'm reading a book I like painful and it's like
this is an electron.
I don't like
white.